[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas：那么让我们看看我们刚才概述的攻击。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: So let's look at the attack that we've just outlined.
所以我们得到了一个全局变量，我称之为stash。
So we've got a global variable, I'm calling it stash.
有人提出了一个全局变量，它就是这样的。
Someone suggested a global variable and there it is.
然后我们将存储到推送函数中
Then we will store into push a function
它将接受这个并将其存储在那个全局变量中。
which will take this and store it in that global variable.
然后为了得到这个要执行的函数，调用append。
And then in order to get to this function to be executed, you call append.
append将调用推送，因为这是一个方法调用，
append will call the push, and because this is a method invocation,
这将被绑定到数组。
this will be bound to the array.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：所以这次攻击利用了其中的几个混淆
&gt;&gt; Douglas: So this attack exploits several confusions that are in this
语言。
language.
原则上的困惑是，在这种语言中没有数组。
The principle confusion is, there are not arrays in this language.
它们的行为与其他语言中的数组不同。
They don't behave like arrays in other languages.
但我们认为我们做到了，甚至是那些构建JavaScript引擎的人，
But we think that we do and even the people who built JavaScript engines,
当他们看到这个问题时，
when they were shown this problem,
他们知道JavaScript中的数组是如何工作的，至少比任何人都要好。
they know how arrays in JavaScript work, at least better than anybody.
他们看不到它，因为每个人都认为这就是数组的作用。
And they couldn't see it because everybody thinks this is what arrays do.
所以当你有这个的时候，我在这里，即使我们知道我们没有
So when you have this I here, even though we know we don't have
在这种语言中，每个人都认为它是int，对吗？
ints in this language, everybody thinks it's an int, right?
所以任何人都不会想到这可能是其他任何东西。
So it doesn't occur to anybody that this could be anything else.
但这只是一把钥匙，对吧？
But it's just a key, right?
事实上，JavaScript将做的是，它将接受您传入的任何内容。
That in fact what JavaScript will do is it will take whatever you pass in.
如果这里不是字符串，它会把它变成字符串。
If it's not a string here it will turn it into a string.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：JavaScript就是这么做的，但是
&gt;&gt; Douglas: That's what JavaScript does but
这不是我们认为编程语言应该表现的，对吗？
that's not how we think a programming language should behave, right?
当你的系统做了一些与我们期望的不同的事情时，
And when you have a system that does something other than what we expect,
您会得到混淆，并且混淆可能会导致安全漏洞，就像本例中一样。
you get confusion and confusion can lead to security exploits, as in this case.
这个问题的另一个来源是
The other source of this problem is that
语言中的所有变量绑定都是静态的，因为函数作用域，
all variable bindings in the language are static, because functions scope,
如果在那里定义了数组，那么这个数组将绑定到那个数组。
if array is defined there then this one will be bound to that one.
除了这个，它是可以预测的。
It's predictable with the exception of this.
这是动态绑定的。
This is bound dynamically.
所以很难推断这个的价值会是多少
And so it's much harder to reason about what the value of this is gonna be at any
即时，因为它可以根据调用的位置和
instant because it can be different depending on where it's called and
当它被称为。
when it's called.
结果是，如果你在考虑系统的安全性或者
And that turns out, if you're thinking about the security of systems or
系统的可靠性，是一件坏事。
the reliability of systems, to be a bad thing.
这就是为什么我更喜欢尝试用这种语言进行编程的方法
That's why I prefer to try to figure out ways of programming in this language
这并不依赖于这一点，因为这往往是不可靠的。
that don't depend on this since this tends to be unreliable.
那么你对这个问题的看法，是不是很有趣？
So what you think of that problem, is that interesting?
所以，现在你明白了袭击的原因，
So, now that you understand the attack,
您将如何更正此代码以防止攻击发生？
how would you correct this code to prevent that attack from happening?
是吗？
Yeah?
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：仅为表扬，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Just to give credit,
文森特在聊天室我想他比我们先拿到这个，但是
Vincent in the chat room I think he had got this a little bit before we did, but
然后他说要修复它，他只是将(I)强制为int，比如+i。
then he's saying to fix it, he would just force the (i) to an int, like +i.
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: That's exactly right.
我也会这么做的。
I would do that too.
所以，我会在这里放一个+i。
So, I would put a +i here.
这样做的结果是加号将字符串转换为数字。
What that accomplishes is is plus will turn the string into a number.
如果你传入一个数字，它只是保持一个数字，所以它是一个无操作。
If you pass in a number, it just stays a number so it's a no op.
但是如果你传入Push这个词，它会把它变成一个数字。
But if you pass in the word push, it will turn it into a number.
PUSH变成什么数字？
What number does push turn into?
NaN，然后将NaN转换为字符串。
NaN, and so then turn NaN into a string.
因此，我们将把v存储在arra.NaN中，这很愚蠢，但至少它不是push。
So, we'll be storing v at array.NaN which is stupid but at least it's not push.
对，所以我们绕过这一点。
Right, so we get around that.
我们可以做的另一件事是不使用推，
The other thing we could do is not use push,
取而代之的是，使用老式的方法为当前长度赋值。
instead use the old fashioned way of assigning to the current length.
这说明了我认为语言中的另一个设计错误
This illustrates another design error in the language that I think
像追加到数组这样基本的东西应该是一个运算符。
something as fundamental as appending to an array should be an operator.
它应该是建立在语言中的东西，不可能是
It should be something that's just built into the language which can't be
被破坏了，但它不是。
corrupted, but it's not.
JavaScript允许，而且还有关于这些如何获得磅的奇怪方式。
JavaScript allows, and there's also the weird way of about how these get pound.
因此，通常在调用push方法时，
So, ordinarily you would when you call push method,
您将使用继承的array.prototype.push。
you're going to be using the inherited array.prototype.push.
但是当我们使用store将我们自己的push属性分配给这个对象时，
But when we assigned our own push property to this object using store,
现在推送是本地的，所以我们看起来不是array.prototype.push。
now push is local and so we don't look array.prototype.push.
这也不符合大多数人的心态
And that again doesn't match most people's mindset about how
编程语言应该可以工作。
programming language should work.
这可能不是您希望此函数成为的那种行为
That's probably not the kind of behavior that you want this function to be
可以修改。
able to to modify.
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：那么你对这个问题有什么看法，是不是很有趣，
&gt;&gt; Douglas: So what do you think of that problem, was that fun,
有趣吗？
was that interesting?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yes.
道格拉斯：先生。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Sir.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：是吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yeah?
为什么不直接给JavaScript实数组，它会破坏它吗？
Why not just give JavaScript real arrays, is it going to break it?
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：当然，打破它。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Absolutely, break it.
是的，互联网上到处都是代码
Yeah, there's code all over the Internet
这就假设了这个可怕的行为&gt；&gt；Speaker 3：and
that assumes this terrible behavior &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: And
你不能只说ECMA6是一个新的标准，有一个新的。
you can't just say that ECMA 6 is a new standard that has a new.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：我希望，顺便说一句，网络不同于任何
&gt;&gt; Douglas: I wish, the way, the web is unlike any
其他平台，如果你正在开发一个服务器，
other platform in that, if you're developing a server,
您可以指定在哪个版本级别上安装什么软件，等等。
you dictate what software is installed on that at what revision level and so on.
您可以控制服务器上发生的一切，因此
You've got control over everything happening on the server so
你可以口授这些东西。
you can dictate that stuff.
所以你可以容忍突破性的变化，因为你决定什么时候
And so you can tolerate breaking changes because you decide when you're going to
做出改变。
make the change.
但在网络上，你必须与任何人被安装的东西一起运行。
But on the web, you have to run with what ever it is that someone's got installed.
如果他们正在运行一些可怕的旧东西，您的代码仍然可以运行
And if they're running some awful old thing your code is still expected to run
在那个旧东西上。
on that old thing.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：所以对于ECMA 6，他们必须有一些新的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So for ECMA 6, they're gonna have to have some new.
对不起，我不知道怎么继续，对不起，
I'm sorry, I don't how to continue, sorry to,
他们必须有一个新的东西可以吃ECMA 6，对吗？
they're gonna have to have a new stuff that can eat ECMA 6, right?
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：对。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Right.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 3：那么为什么不创建一个新的东西而不是一个数组，称之为列表。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So why not create a new thing instead of an array, call it a list.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：他们可以这样做，事实上他们已经在ES6中添加了新内容，因为
&gt;&gt; Douglas: They could do that, in fact they have added new things in ES6, for
例如，有一种叫做地图的新东西，它的行为就像对象应该表现的那样。
example, there's a new thing called a map which behaves like objects should behave.
它更像是一个哈希表，并且
It is more correctly like a hash table and
有新的形式可以做到这一点，但它看起来不是这样的。
there are new forms for doing that but it doesn't look like this.
因此很难让人们使用它，因为它没有
And so it's gonna be very difficult to get people to use it because it doesn't have
这一句法的便利之处在于
the syntactic conveniences that this one
道格拉斯：是的，所以-
has &gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah, so the-
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：我知道有好的
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: I know there are good
这些事情的答案，我只是&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：不，
answers for these things, I'm just &gt;&gt; Douglas: No,
我不是想让它消失，我是说，网络真的是，
I'm not trying to wave it off, I mean, the web is a really,
一旦我们在Web标准中犯了一个错误，我们就会被它卡住。
once we make a mistake in a web standard we're stuck with it.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：[笑]&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：我们所能做的就是继续
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Douglas: And all we can do is pile on
更多的错误在它上面，我们不能纠正任何曾经的东西
more mistakes on top of it, we can't correct any of the stuff that's ever been
完成了[大笑]，所以你们都知道使用Web标准是令人难以置信的
done [LAUGH] And so working with web standards as you all know is incredibly
令人沮丧，因为没有什么会变得更好，它只会变得更大。
frustrating because nothing ever gets better, it just gets bigger.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：他们没有去掉空白标签。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: They didn't get rid of the blank tag.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：嗯，不完全是。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Well, not entirely.
我的意思是你仍然可以写眨眼，而且不会再让你头疼了，但是
I mean you can still write blink and it's not gonna give you headaches anymore, but
它仍然被允许，它仍然在DOM中构建结构，它仍然在那里。
it's still allowed, it's still building structures in the Dom, it's still there.
事实上，您可以编写CSS，这将使闪烁恢复生机。
And in fact, you can write CSS, which will cause the blink to come back to life.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：[听不到][大笑]&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：所以是[大笑]
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: [INAUDIBLE] [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Douglas: So it's [LAUGH]
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：是的，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Yeah,
人们已经用CSS编写了JavaScript插件。
people have written JavaScript plugins in CSS.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：是的，它-&gt；&gt；扬声器4：带来
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah, it- &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Bring
返回GeoCities页面。
back the geocities page.
把眨眼的东西拿回来。
Bring back the blink.
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：是的，修复Web非常困难。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah, it's very, very hard to fix the Web.
因为当错误发生时，错误的问题
Cuz when something wrong happens, the problem with the wrong
事情并不是它们毫无用处，而是它们很危险，很奇怪。
things isn't that they're useless, it's that they're dangerous and weird.
还有一些非常聪明的人会说哇，
And there are very clever people who will go wow,
太糟糕了，我能用它做什么？
that's crappy, what can I do with that?
他们会想出来的。
And they'll figure it out.
他们会拿走你见过的最愚蠢的东西，现在它变成了
They'll take the stupidest thing you ever saw and it now becomes
一些流行图书馆的一部分，我们再也摆脱不了它了。
part of some popular library and we can't get rid of it anymore.